hothardware.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy, Terms, Conditions and Copyright | HotHardware

**Privacy, Terms, Conditions and Copyright Policy of Hot Hardware, Inc.  
**   
HotHardware.com takes your privacy seriously. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of the information we collect. We encourage you to read our full privacy policy, below:   
**  
Information Collected**  
HotHardware.com does not directly collect any personally identifiable information about individuals, except when such information is voluntarily submitted by the user. In common with many websites, HotHardware.com automatically logs certain non-personally identifiable information about visits to our websites. This information is used for system administration and for producing usage statistics. We do collect email addresses from individuals that wish to take advantage of special promotional offers and our mailing lists, but we do not sell, rent or disclose collected email addresses to third parties.

**Cookies  
**We may automatically collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our services and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our services. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services.

 **What Cookies Do We Use?**

Below is a list of each category of cookies we use and why we use each cookie. First party cookies are our own cookies set by HotHardware, Inc., controlled by us and used to provide information about the usage of the Service.

**Essential Cookies or Strictly Necessary Cookies:** These cookies are essential to the Service in order for you to move around the Service and to use its features. Without these cookies, certain features could not function. No information about your browsing habits is gathered by these cookies.

**Functional Cookies:** These cookies remember how you prefer to use the Service and enable us to improve the way the Service works. We can remember your settings and help provide you with ads. Functional Cookies are persistent cookies that the Service remembers when your computer or device comes back to that Service.

**Analytics Cookies:** Analytics Cookies allow us to improve our services by collecting information about your use of the Service. We use these cookies to help improve how the website works. For example, Analytics Cookies show us statistics, which are the most frequently visited pages on the Service, help us record any difficulties you have with the Service, and show us whether our advertising is effective or not. We can’t identify you personally through the use of these cookies, but third parties who provide these cookies may be able to.

**Behavioral Advertising Cookies:** Behavioral Advertising Cookies are used to deliver relevant advertisements to users both on and off the Service. We analyze what pages you visit on these sites, what products or services you view, and whether you view or click on ads that are shown to you. We may also use a cookie to learn whether someone who saw an ad later visited and took an action on the advertiser’s site. We use this information to send you interest-based ads and may also share this information with third parties. Similarly, our partners may use a cookie to determine whether we’ve shown an ad and how it performed, or provide us with information about how you interact with ads. We may also work with a partner to show you an ad on or off the Service, such as after you have visited a partner’s site or application.

**Third Party Cookies:** Some of the cookies on the Service are operated by third parties, such as Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+, Reddit, YouTube, Facebook or Comscore. Some of these third parties (for example third-party advertisers) may use cookies on the Service, in emails or in our advertisements on other websites to allow them to deliver the services they are providing. Some of the cookies operated by third parties may be used for analytics purposes, such as to monitor, analyze and prevent fraudulent traffic or other suspicious activities. In order to create a user-friendly experience, some of our third-party promotions and advertisements are designed to automatically transmit users’ information onto the third party’s landing page when you choose to “click” upon a third party’s advertisement or promotion. We do not control these third parties or their use of cookies. This means it is not possible for us to manage these cookies. This Policy only covers the use of cookies by HotHardware, Inc. and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party. Some of these third party cookies are not session based and have varying expiry dates. Please check the websites of these third parties for details on how they use cookies.

**Flash Cookies:** We may, in certain situations, use Adobe Flash Player to deliver special content, such as video clips or animation. Flash cookies are stored on your device, but they are managed through an interface that is different from the one provided by your web browser. This means that it is not possible to manage Flash cookies at the browser level in the same way you would manage other types of cookies. Instead, you can access your Flash management tools from Adobe’s website directly. See Adobe’s [website](https://www.adobe.com/devnet/security.html).

**Geo-Location Information:** Some devices allow applications to access real-time location-based information (for example, GPS). Some photos or other content you place within the Service may contain recorded location information. We may use this information to optimize your experience. Also, some of the information we collect from a device, for example IP address, can sometimes be used to approximate a device’s location.

**Web Beacons**  
HotHardware, Inc partners and 3rd party contractors may collect information using web beacons (also known as pixel tags). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Services or in our emails. We use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness or to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. 

**Opt-Out Policy**  
HotHardware.com gives users options to opt out wherever practical; such choices include:

  * Opting not to receive our electronic newsletters when registering for a site
  * Opting not to receive review site notifications
  * Refusing cookies which may affect site and service functionality or disable it completely

**Unsubscribe Policy**  
Users may unsubscribe from any of our electronic newsletters or site notifications at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter or notification.

**Use of Collected Information**  
Collecting the information described above enables us to tailor our content to our readers' needs and to target more relevant advertising. If at any time you would like assistance with deleting your data, please contact us as  [admin@hothardware.com](mailto:admin@hothardware.com)

**Third Party Partners**  
HotHardware.com has teamed up with reputable third party vendors in order to provide certain services to its online users. When leaving our website to view one of our partner websites, we encourage users to review the privacy statements of those websites as we cannot guarantee the privacy of users while visiting affiliate sites. HotHardware.com may use third-party companies to serve ads or analyze behavior patterns when you visit our Web site. These companies may place or provide ads (such as banner ads) on this Web site that might also place cookies. These companies may use non-personally or personally identifiable information about your visit to our web site in order to help us improve our user experience and/or provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of providing these services or placing these ads, these third-party companies may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer and each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies.

Our primary partners are the following and we encourage you to visit their privacy policies to see how they might use your data:  
[Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy) \- Google Analytics Tracking, Google AdX Advertising, Google [DFP Ad Serving](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)  
[Mailchimp](https://kb.mailchimp.com/accounts/management/about-mailchimp-the-eu-swiss-privacy-shield-and-the-gdpr) \- Email/Newsletter Services  
[Feedblitz](https://www.feedblitz.com/privacy) \- Email/Newsletter Services  
[Po.st/RythmOne](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy) \- Site Social Sharing Widget  
[Revcontent](https://faq.revcontent.com/customer/en/portal/articles/2703838-revcontent-s-privacy-and-cookie-policy) \- Native Advertising  
[Disqus](https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy) \- Site Comments Engine  
[YAF.net](http://www.yetanotherforum.net/privacy) \- Site Forum Software  
[YouTube](https://policies.google.com/privacy) \- Site Video Services  
[Ziff Davis](https://www.ziffdavis.com/privacy-policy) \- Advertising  
[IDG Tech Network](https://www.idg.com/gdpr/) \- Advertising  
[Sovrn Holdings, Inc](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/) \- Advertising  
[Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496) \- Merchant Sales Services  
[Commission Junction/Conversant Media](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy) \- Merchant Sales Services

For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit: <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and <https://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

**How this Privacy Policy May Change**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and all changes will be effective at the time we post them. If we believe there is a significant change to this Privacy Policy or our data collection and use practices, we will indicate on our website that our Privacy Policy has changed prior to the change becoming effective. The then-posted version of the Privacy Policy supersedes all prior versions. Your continued access to or use of any of the Services shall be deemed your acceptance of the Privacy Policy. 

**Use of This Site**  
As a reader or user of HotHardware.com, you are using the site as a privilege, not a right, free of charge. Therefore the owner and operators of this site may, at any time, at their discretion, disable/ban your user account or prevent your use of this site. 

**Indemnity**  
You will indemnify and hold harmless HotHardware.com, its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, customers, vendors, officers and employees from any liability, damage or cost (including reasonable attorneys. fees and cost) from any claim or demand made by any third party or yourself, due to or arising out of your access to the Site, use of the Services, violation of the Terms of Use by you, or the infringement by you, or any third party using your account or HotHardware.com User ID, or of any intellectual property or other right of any person or entity. 

**Acceptance of Terms**  
By using the HotHardware.com website, you signify your acceptance of this website privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. Your continued use of any HotHardware.com site following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of those changes.

If you have questions about our privacy or legal policies, contact us via email at: [admin@hothardware.com](mailto:admin@hothardware.com)

**Copyright Policy:**  
We respect the intellectual property and copyright of others. As such, we have a policy of removing user submissions that violate copyright law, suspending access to our services and to any user who uses the services in violation of copyright law, as well as terminating, in appropriate circumstances, the account of any user who uses our services in violation of copyright law. 

Pursuant to Title 17 of the United States Code, Section 512, we have implemented procedures for receiving written notification of claimed copyright infringement and for processing claims in accordance with the law. If you believe a user of HotHardware.com's service is infringing your copyright, please provide written notice to our agent listed below for notice of claims of copyright infringement and we will expeditiously remove the allegedly infringing material.

**DMCA Notification of Claimed Infringement:**  
If you believe that your content has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us with written notice that includes the following information:

  * Your name, address, telephone number, and email address.
  * A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed.
  * The URL(s) or a description of where on the HotHardware.com service the material you claim is infringing is located.
  * A written statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the use of the copyrighted work is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  * A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.
  * An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest.

Send your notice to our agent for notices of claimed copyright infringement as follows:

Email: [copyright@hothardware.com](mailto:copyright@hothardware.com)

Postal mail:   
Hot Hardware, Inc.  
C/O Saunders & Silverstein, LLP.  
14 Cedar Street - Suite 224    
Amesbury, MA 01913  
Fax: 978.463.9109

**DMCA Counter-notification:**

  * If you believe your material has been removed in error, please provide us with a written counter-notification that includes the following information:
  * Your name, address, telephone number, and email address.
  * A description of the material that was removed.
  * The URL(s) or a description of where on the HotHardware.com service the material appeared prior to removal.
  * A statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or misidentification.
  * A statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of the Federal District Court for the judicial district in which your address is located, or if your address is outside of the United States, any judicial district in which HotHardware.com may be found, and that you will accept service of process from the person who filed the original DMCA notice or an agent of that person.
  * Your electronic or physical signature, or the signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf.

Send your notice to our agent for notices of claimed copyright infringement as follows:

Email: [copyright@hothardware.com](mailto:copyright@hothardware.com)

Postal mail:   
Hot Hardware, Inc.  
C/O Saunders & Silverstein, LLP.  
14 Cedar Street - Suite 224    
Amesbury, MA 01913  
Fax: 978.463.9109
